{
    "subject": "resource/Sprite_(computer_graphics)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sprite_(computer_graphics)",
    "human_readable": "The topic of Sprite (computer graphics) is primarily about Sprite (computer graphics).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9044910073280334,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of the topic 'Sprite (computer graphics)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.893607497215271,
            "question": "Can you explain what a Sprite is in the context of computer graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246012687683105,
            "question": "How have advancements in technology affected the way Sprites are used in computer graphics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5184202790260315,
            "question": "How are Sprites different from other graphical elements like textures or models?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49258869886398315,
            "question": "What are some common uses for Sprites in video games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4919808506965637,
            "question": "What factors influence the appearance and behavior of a Sprite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4408930838108063,
            "question": "What are some techniques used to animate Sprites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43893423676490784,
            "question": "What are the limitations of using Sprites in complex graphical environments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3719375729560852,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of popular games that use Sprites effectively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3603220283985138,
            "question": "What role do Sprites play in the overall visual design of a game or application?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The topic of Sprite (computer graphics) is primarily about Sprite (computer graphics).",
            "html": "dbpedia_988_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of popular games that use Sprites effectively?",
            "html": "dbpedia_988_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the limitations of using Sprites in complex graphical environments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_988_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some techniques used to animate Sprites?",
            "html": "dbpedia_988_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_988_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents provide a comprehensive explanation of what sprites are in computer graphics.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various definitions and usages of the term \"sprite\" in computer graphics, confirming that the topic of sprite indeed relates to sprites used in computer graphics, including their historical use in video games."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}